<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Speechnotes team on</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/contributors/speechnotes-team/</link><description>Recent content in The Speechnotes team on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:25:12 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://speechnotes.co/contributors/speechnotes-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Affiliate Program Updated Rates</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/blog/affiliate-program-updated-rates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/blog/affiliate-program-updated-rates/</guid><description>Speechnotes Transcription Service Affiliate Program Now Offers 20% Revenue Share for Life # We are thrilled to announce an exciting update to the Speechnotes affiliate program! Starting today, our affiliates will earn 20% revenue share for life on all referrals. This is a huge opportunity for partners looking to promote a trusted speech-to-text tool and earn long-term passive income.
&amp;ndash; Please note this is currently only for Speechnotes Transcribe and not for the Speechnotes mobile app or online notepad.</description></item><item><title>Speechnotes' New WhatsApp bot for Transcription</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/blog/speechnotes-new-whatsapp-bot-for-transcription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/blog/speechnotes-new-whatsapp-bot-for-transcription/</guid><description>We’re excited to announce that Speechnotes has just launched a brand-new WhatsApp bot designed to make voice transcription even easier and more accessible. With our bot, you can transcribe any WhatsApp voice message in seconds – and even get it translated if needed – all for free!
Watch the demo Video # How Does It Work? # It’s super simple:
Add the bot to your contacts using this number: +1-343-321-1114. Forward any voice message from your WhatsApp chats to the bot.</description></item><item><title>Speechnotes VS Rev - Live Test</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/blog/speechnotes-vs-rev-live-test/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/blog/speechnotes-vs-rev-live-test/</guid><description>The Big AI Transcription Battle: Speechnotes vs. Rev # Welcome to the big AI Transcription Battle! Automatic transcription is evolving as novel AI models bring transcription accuracy to near-human or even better-than-human levels. Along with big benefits in pricing, speed (real-time results), and privacy (no one is listening to your recordings), the competition is fierce.
We decided to do a head-to-head battle between two leading AI transcription service providers: Speechnotes &amp;amp; Rev.</description></item><item><title>Exciting New Partnership with Microsoft</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/blog/exciting-new-partnership-with-microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/blog/exciting-new-partnership-with-microsoft/</guid><description>WellSource Ltd. Accepted into Microsoft for Startups - Founders Hub Program # We are excited to announce that in July 2023, WellSource Ltd., the company behind Speechnotes, was officially accepted into the Microsoft for Startups - Founders Hub Program.
What Does This Mean for Speechnotes? # Being part of Microsoft for Startups is a huge milestone for us. The Founders Hub program provides access to invaluable resources, tools, and support from Microsoft, which will allow us to continue growing and improving Speechnotes.</description></item></channel></rss>