<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speechotes Manuals on</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Speechotes Manuals on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dictation Quick Start</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/quick-start-dictation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/quick-start-dictation/</guid><description>Quick Start # Go to here Click the mic Approve microphone Start dictating Optional - select a different dictation language Upgrade here Demo video # Detailed Instructions # Pre-operation: # Connect a high-quality microphone to your PC (if you have a built-in microphone it might be good enough). Operation: # Click the mic
For the first time only: Your browser will popup a request for you to allow the site to listen to your mic.</description></item><item><title>Transcription Quick Start</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/quick-start-transcription/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/quick-start-transcription/</guid><description>Short Demo # See Real Life Examples # For a quick overview of how Speechnotes Transcribe works, you can see some real life examples of transcriptions done by Speechnotes. Here are some samples
Start &amp;amp; Sign In # Go to Speechnotes Transcribe web page at https://speechnotes.co/transcribe/ Tap the 'SIGN IN' and sign in using your Google account. No need to remember new passwords. Speechnotes will not receive your password - it remains private - it only receives your email address and confirmation from Google that indeed you signed in.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://speechnotes.co/docs/guides/privacy/</guid><description>General # We at Speechnotes, Speechlogger, TextHear, Speechkeys value your privacy, and that's why we do not store anything you say or type or in fact any other data about you - unless it is solely needed for the purpose of your operation. We don't share it with 3rd parties, other than Google / Microsoft for the speech-to-text engine. Handling recordings and results # - Transcription service # Our transcription service is probably the most private and secure transcription service available.</description></item></channel></rss>